(Penny:)...that I didn't understand.
(Leonard:)It's actually a pretty simple process.
You see, cyanoacrylates are monomers,
which polymerize--
(Howard(arriving):)Red alert. Leonard, Sheldon ran away.
(Leonard:)Man, I cannot catch a break.
(Penny:)So how do you know he ran away?
I mean, he's not answering his phone,
he handed in his resignation...
(Howard:)...and he sent me a text that said,
"I'm running away."
Okay. Thanks for letting me know.
(Penny:)Well-- Leonard.
Aren't you gonna do something?
Well, of course
I'm gonna do something.
Uh, Howard, check the comic-book store.
(Leonard:)Raj, go to the Thai restaurant.
I'll stay with Penny in her apartment.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
(Leonard:)Oh, damn it.
(Leonard:)It's Sheldon's mother.
(Leonard:)A break cannot be caught.
(Leonard:)Hi, Mrs. Cooper.
(Leonard:)He is?
(Leonard:)Sheldon went home to Texas.
(Leonard:)Yeah-- No, I know he resigned.
(Leonard:)Yes, I guess it kind of is our fault.